{
    "subject": "resource/Duck_Soup_(1933_film)",
    "predicate": "property/name",
    "object": "Duck Soup",
    "human_readable": "The name of Duck Soup (1933 film) is Duck Soup.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9486376047134399,
            "question": "Is 'Duck Soup' a title of a film?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9369985461235046,
            "question": "Which film is titled 'Duck Soup'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9115462303161621,
            "question": "What is the name of the 1933 film?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8642835021018982,
            "question": "What is the title of the film from 1933?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.85172438621521,
            "question": "When was the movie 'Duck Soup' made?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8388099670410156,
            "question": "What is the title of the 1933 movie?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8153919577598572,
            "question": "In what year was the film Duck Soup released?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.811747133731842,
            "question": "What was the name given to the film released in 1933?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6324847340583801,
            "question": "What is the name of the film?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.556163489818573,
            "question": "Tell me the name of the movie released in 1933."
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The name of Duck Soup (1933 film) is Duck Soup.",
            "html": "dbpedia_7704_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of the film?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7704_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What was the name given to the film released in 1933?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7704_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=In what year was the film Duck Soup released?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7704_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7704_125.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7704_159.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7704_166.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7704_24.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7704_35.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7704_40.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7704_42.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7704_44.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7704_50.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7704_64.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents clearly state that the title of the 1933 Marx Brothers movie is \"Duck Soup,\" thus supporting the triple."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Very Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}